http://www.fypon.com/pages/privacy-policy

Sadly, Internet Explorer is not supported.
×
Fypon is best experienced on...
Updated Date - 8/28/2019
This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") describes our privacy practices for the websites where it is posted and does not cover other websites not owned or operated by us. If you have any questions regarding our privacy practices, you can contact us as described below.
Important: By using the Site, you agree to and accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
Information We Collect
We collect PII: We may collect Personally-Identifiable Information ("PII") from you, but only if you provide it voluntarily. PIl refers to any information that uniquely identifies or can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a specific person. This may mean:
your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, title, birth date, gender, employer or company name and business details, purchasing data, language, nationality, work and/or professional experience and skill set and salary;
the name and email address of another person provided to us by you;
information for using online registration and/or payment options or otherwise managing a user account.
We collect demographic information: We passively collect anonymous information. One manner of collecting such information is through cookies, which are small bits of data stored on your computer based on your Internet activity. You may configure your browser to reject cookies but, if you do so, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Site. We may use cookies, pixel tags, clear GIFs, Google Analytics or other third-party analytics and other similar technology. We use this information to measure the use of the Site and to improve the Site. This demographic information may include:
the referring domain name, your internet protocol (IP) addresses, your browser type, and your operating system type.
to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the Site, pages viewed, and other similar information
We may collect Credit Card Information: If you provide us with any credit card information, we use that information only accordance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (PCI-DSS). You may be redirected to a third-party credit card processor, including, but not limited to, Pay Pal, Paymetric, Verisign, Oracle iStore, and Geo Trust. If you submit payment through any third-party processor or entity, you are subject to the third party's applicable privacy policy and terms of use.
How We Use Information (including PII) That We CollectWhen you provide us with PII, we may use that information to:
comply with legal requirements;
to communicate with you in response to your submissions to us;
to respond to your employment submission(s) and/or request(s);
to provide you with information relating to us and our products and/or services, including but not limited to e-newsletters, sweepstakes, promotions, new product details or offers, marketing materials, and customized advertisements particular to your interests and/or previous experiences with us;
to process payments relating to purchases you make;
to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services
to enforce the applicable Terms of Use or Legal Notice governing the Site; and
to notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy, the applicable Terms of Use, Legal Notice or other applicable policies or terms that affect you and your use of the Site.
Do We Share Your Information With Third Parties?
We may share your PII and anonymous information for our businesses purposes and as legally permitted. For example, we may share:
With entities that perform functions on our behalf or in partnership with us. These third parties may have access to the information you have provided via the Site, including any PII, only to the extent it is necessary to perform their duties and functions for us. All such use will be subject to this Privacy Policy. Except for where you consent to a disclosure and for disclosed joint marketing arrangements, we do not market, sell or rent Pll to third parties.
We may disclose Pll for legal compliance purposes, to protect our companies, and in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose Pll in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe it is necessary to protect the confidentiality and security of our records pertaining to you, to limit our legal liability or to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or as otherwise required or permitted by law.
Within our family of companies. For example, we might share with one of our related companies, which include others in the Fortune Brands Home & Security family (see here for a list). If we do so, they will use your information as described in their own privacy policies.
Cross-Border TransfersWe may transfer Pll across country borders within our company (but at all times in compliance with this Privacy Policy). If you are located in the EU, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to and stored in the United States. By using this site or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer to the United States.
ChildrenThe Site is not directed at children, and we do not knowingly collect any Pll from children under thirteen years of age unless the collection complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). If we discover that a child under the age of thirteen (13) years has provided us with PII, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that child's Pll from our systems.
Links To Other Sites This Sitemay contain links to other sites, including but not limited to Facebook, YouTube and Twitter. While we try to link only to reputable sites that respect your privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of other sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us on this site and does not apply to third party sites.
How We Protect Your InformationWhile we have put in place measures that we deem reasonable to safeguard information that we collect from you, due to the nature of the Internet we cannot guarantee the security of any information on or transmitted over the Internet. As a result, we make no warranty regarding the security of any information you transmit to us via the Site and you do so at your own risk.
Policy ChangesWe reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. In the event that we make a material change to our policy we may post a notice of the change on the Site. All changes and modifications to the Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date the modified Privacy Policy is posted on the Site. We will not use Pll in a manner materially different than as described in the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the information was collected.
Contacting UsIf you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy for this site or its implementation, if you wish to update or correct your personally identifiable information, you may contact us by phone at (800)-446-3040, by mail at: Fypon Attn: Marketing Department, 1750 Indian Wood Circle, Maumee, OH 43537, or by email at cps@fypon.com. Whether contacting us by phone, mail or email, please include the specific website to which your request relates so that we may ensure timely and efficient resolution of your request. We will contact any person lodging a formal complaint or requesting a correction to his/her personally identifiable information and will cooperate with appropriate regulatory authorities to resolve any complaints that cannot be resolved between us and any individual(s). You should be aware that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases without some residual data because of backups and other reasons.
AssignabilityIf we are involved in a merger, acquisition, consolidation, the sale of substantially all of our assets, or any other corporate transfer, exchange or restructuring, whatever form it may take, we may transfer your information to one or more successor entities in the transaction(s).
Governing LawYou further agree that this Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Ohio and the United States of America. Any dispute under or related to this Privacy Policy shall be brought exclusively in the state or federal courts in Wood County and STATE of Ohio, United States of America.
Language DiscrepanciesIn the event there is a discrepancy or inconsistency between the English language version and any translated version of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise provided by law, the English version shall prevail and govern.
California Controlled Privacy
Find more here
Our Company
About Fypon
Newsroom
Find a Dealer
International Dealers
Support
Fypon is the "most used brand" for interior decorative mouldings, trim, and columns by builders, builders-developers and general contractors.
Fypon is the "most used brand" for interior decorative mouldings, trim, and columns by builders, builders-developers and general contractors.
Thanks for signing up to Fypon's Newsletter!
Close
